Guide to the Central Washington University Office of the President, Jerilyn S, McIntyre Papers 1992-2010 (bulk 2000-2008)
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
Central Washington University Office of the President, Jerilyn S, McIntyre Papers
1992-2010 (bulk 2000-2008)
Central Washington University, Archives and Special Collections 400 E University Way Ellensburg, WA 98926 (509) 963-1717 http://www.lib.cwu.edu/Archives-Special-Collections archive@cwu.edu
RG014-05-36
Central Washington University, Office of the President
21 linear feet 38 letter-sized Hollinger boxes, 6 half letter-sized Hollinger boxes, 1 card file box
This collection comprises materials relevant to the presidency of Jerilyn S, McIntyre at Central Washington University, 2000-2008.
Biographical Note
Jerilyn Sue McIntyre was born on June 24, 1942, to Frank Otto and Maxine (Ward) McIntyre. She attended Stanford University, receiving a Bachelor of Arts degree in history in 1964. The following year she acquired a Master of Arts degree in journalism from Stanford. From 1965 to 1967, she worked as a correspondent for McGraw-Hill Publishing Company at their World News Bureau in Los Angeles. In 1968, after obtaining a teaching certificate, she was hired as an Assistant Professor in the Department of Mass Communications at Chico State College in California. In 1973 she attained a Ph.D. in Communications from the University of Washington and later the same year, took a position as Assistant Professor in the School of Journalism at the University of Iowa. Dr. McIntyre remained there until 1977, when she was hired as Associate Professor in the Department of Communications at the University of Utah. While at the University of Utah, she served as Associate Dean of the College of Humanities from 1984 to 1988, Associate Vice President for Academic Affairs from 1988-1990, Vice President for Academic Affairs from 1990-1998, and briefly as interim President in 1991 and for the entire year of 1997. Dr. McIntyre became President of Central Washington University in the summer of 2000.
Included in this collection are notes, schedules, programs, newspaper clippings, scrapbooks, and media materials relevant to the presidency of Jerilyn S, McIntyre at Central Washington University, 2000-2008.
This collection incorporates three previously processed collections: RG014-05-59, Office of the President, Inauguration Records of Jerilyn S, McIntyre; RG014-05-36, Office of the President, Jerilyn Sue McIntyre, President’s Notes; and RG014-05-61, Office of the President, Calendar of Events for Jerilyn S, McIntyre,
Central Washington University began as the Washington State Normal School in 1891. In 1937, the school was rechristened the Central Washington College of Education. In 1961, the school became Central Washington State College and, finally, in 1977, Central Washington University.
This collection is divided into eleven series:
I, Personnel Records
II, Inauguration
III, Planning Priorities
IV, Calendar of Events
V, Professional Activities
VI, Speeches
VII, Board of Trustees Minutes
VIII, Meeting Notes
IX, Retirement
X, Scrapbooks
XI, Media Materials
This collection was organized by its creator. Items within each series are, by and large, arranged alphabetically and chronologically. The collection has been organized to reflect the progression of Jerilyn McIntyre’s career. Summaries and planning priorities have been placed at the beginning of the collection to provide an introduction to McIntyre’s presidency.
The majority of this collection is open to the public for educational research; however, access to some materials may be restricted.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Central Washington University, Office of the President
Ellensburg (Wash.)
Central Washington University--History; Washington (State)--History; McIntyre, Jerilyn S.
Washington (State); Colleges and Universities
- Personnel Records, I
  - Annual leave, 2003-2008 (Box-folder 1-1)
  - Biography, circa 2000s (Box-folder 1-2)
  - Contract amendment, 2008 (Box-folder 1-3)
  - Evaluations, 2001-2007 (Box-folder 1-4)
  - L-5 Reports, 2001-2009 (Box-folder 1-5)
  - Leave, 2009 (Box-folder 1-6)
  - Miscellaneous, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 1-7)
  - President Emeritus salary and benefits, 2008-2010 (Box-folder 1-8)
  - President salary and benefits, 2000-2009 (Box-folder 1-9)
  - Public disclosure, 2000-2007 (Box-folder 1-10)
  - Telework reports, 2009 (Box-folder 1-11)
  - Transition briefings, 2000 (Box-folder 1-12)
  - Transition details, 2000 (Box-folder 1-13)
  - Transition details, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 1-14)
  - W, David Smith, 2000-2008 (Box-folder 1-15)
- Inauguration, II
  - Advance letters, April 2000-May 2000 (Box-folder 2-1)
  - Banquet, 2000 (Box-folder 2-2)
  - Budget and expenses, 2000 (Box-folder 2-3)
  - Ceremony, 2000 (Box-folder 2-4)
  - Certificates of congratulation, 2000 (Box-folder 2-5)
  - Congratulatory notes, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 2-6)
  - Event notes, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 2-7)
  - Facilities arrangements, 2000 (Box-folder 2-8)
  - Grant application, 2000 (Box-folder 2-9)
  - Greetings from Governor Locke, 2000 (Box-folder 2-10)
  - Groundbreaking, 2000 (Box-folder 2-11)
  - Initial notes and messages, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 2-12)
  - Invitations and invitation lists, 2000 (Box-folder 2-13)
  - Lodging, 2000 (Box-folder 2-14)
  - Mace, 1979-2000 (Box-folder 2-15)
  - Medallion, 2000 (Box-folder 2-16)
  - Nelson platform party information, 1992 (Box-folder 2-17)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 (Box-folder 2-18)
  - Parking, 2000 (Box-folder 2-19)
  - Posters, 2000 (Box-folder 2-20)
  - Preliminary meeting, May 2000 (Box-folder 2-21)
  - Presidential Inauguration Committee information, 2000 (Box-folder 2-22)
  - Presidential Inauguration Committee meeting minutes, May 2002-June 2002 (Box-folder 2-23)
  - Presidential selection, 2000 (Box-folder 2-24)
  - Programs, 2000 (Box-folder 2-25)
  - Receptions and dinner, 2000 (Box-folder 2-26)
  - Security, 2000 (Box-folder 2-27)
  - Speakers, 2000 (Box-folder 3-1)
  - Transition meeting, March 2000 (Box-folder 3-2)
- Planning Priorities, III
  - Historical overview, 2008 (Box-folder 3-3)
  - Overview, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 3-4)
  - Strategic planning, 2000 (Box-folder 3-5)
  - Strategic planning, 2001-2006 (Box-folder 3-6)
  - Strategic planning, 2005-2010 (Box-folder 3-7)
  - Budget and planning, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 3-8)
  - Budget and planning, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 3-9)
  - Budget and planning, 2004 (Box-folder 3-10)
  - Budget and planning, 2004 (Box-folder 3-11)
  - Budget and planning, 2005 (Box-folder 3-12)
  - Budget and planning, 2005 (Box-folder 3-13)
  - Budget and planning, 2006 (Box-folder 3-14)
  - Budget and planning, 2007 (Box-folder 3-15)
  - Budget and planning, 2008 (Box-folder 3-16)
  - Budget and planning, Briefings on issues, 2008 (Box-folder 3-17)
  - Budget and planning, Cabinet retreat, 2003 (Box-folder 3-18)
  - Budget and planning, Campus Vision memos, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 3-19)
  - Budget and planning, Data and scenarios, 2008 (Box-folder 3-20)
  - Budget and planning, Documents, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 4-1)
  - Budget and planning, Faculty salaries, 2001-2005 (Box-folder 4-2)
  - Budget and planning, Financials, 2003 (Box-folder 4-3)
  - Budget and planning, High Demand, 2003 (Box-folder 4-4)
  - Budget and planning, Integrated Marketing Proposal, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 4-5)
  - Budget and planning, Performance indicators, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 4-6)
  - Budget and planning, Proposed budget, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 4-7)
  - Budget and planning, Scenarios data, 2008 (Box-folder 4-8)
  - Budget and planning, Spheres of distinction, 2008 (Box-folder 4-9)
  - Budget stabilization, Overview, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 4-10)
  - Budget stabilization, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 4-11)
  - Budget stabilization, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 4-12)
  - Budget stabilization, 2008 (Box-folder 4-13)
  - Budget stabilization, HECB presentation, 2008 (Box-folder 4-14)
  - Building a collaborative team, 2001-2007 (Box-folder 4-15)
  - Entrepreneurial ideas, CWU-label wine program, 2008 (Box-folder 4-16)
  - Entrepreneurial ideas, CWU Research Foundation, History, 1999-2007 (Box-folder 4-17)
  - Entrepreneurial ideas, CWU Research Foundation, Innovation Park, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 4-18)
  - Entrepreneurial ideas, CWU Research Foundation, Records, 2008 (Box-folder 5-1)
  - Entrepreneurial ideas, Program initiatives, 2004 (Box-folder 5-2)
  - Focus on excellence, Showcasing CWU talent, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 5-3)
  - Focus on excellence, Spheres of distinction, 2006-2008 (Box-folder 5-4)
  - Growing enrollment, pre 2000 (Box-folder 5-5)
  - Growing enrollment, 2008 (Box-folder 5-6)
  - Improving external relationships, Overview (Box-folder 5-7)
  - Improving external relationships, Archives project (Box-folder 5-8)
  - Improving external relationships, Campus-community coalition, 2005 (Box-folder 5-9)
  - Improving external relationships, Climate commitment, 2007 (Box-folder 5-10)
  - Improving external relationships, Community partnerships, 2001 (Box-folder 5-11)
  - Improving external relationships, CWU fundraising campaigns, 2005-2010 (Box-folder 5-12)
  - Improving external relationships, Diversity, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 5-13)
  - Improving external relationships, History of CWU Book Project, 2003-2006 (Box-folder 5-14)
  - Improving external relationships, Honorary degrees, 2003 (Box-folder 5-15)
  - Improving visibility and reputation, Overview (Box-folder 5-16)
  - Improving visibility and reputation, Blue Ribbon Commission on Athletics, 2005 (Box-folder 5-17)
  - Improving visibility and reputation, Channel 15, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 5-18)
  - Improving visibility and reputation, Economic Impact Report, 2007 (Box-folder 6-1)
  - Improving visibility and reputation, Guest volumes/editions, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 6-2)
  - Improving visibility and reputation, Legislative and congressional relations, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 6-3)
  - Improving visibility and reputation, Legislative packets and messages, 2004-2007 (Box-folder 6-4)
  - Improving visibility and reputation, Outreach and initiatives, 2003 (Box-folder 6-5)
  - Improving visibility and reputation, Performing Arts and Presidential Speakers series, 2006-2009 (Box-folder 6-6)
  - Improving visibility and reputation, President’s Reports, 2004-2008 (Box-folder 6-7)
  - Improving visibility and reputation, Publicizing distinctions, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 6-8)
  - Integrating planning, Overview (Box-folder 6-9)
  - Integrating planning, Board of Trustees discussions, circa 2008 (Box-folder 6-10)
  - Integrating planning, Budget discussions, 2000-2008 (Box-folder 6-11)
  - Integrating planning, Emergency planning (flu), 2005 (Box-folder 6-12)
- Calendar of Events, IV
  - July-August, 2000 (Box-folder 7-1)
  - September-October, 2000 (Box-folder 7-2)
  - Briefing sheets, November-December, 2000 (Box-folder 7-3)
  - 2001 (Box-folder 7-4)
  - April-May, 2002 (Box-folder 7-5)
  - June, 2002 (Box-folder 8-1)
  - July, 2002 (Box-folder 8-2)
  - August-September, 2002 (Box-folder 8-3)
  - October, 2002 (Box-folder 8-4)
  - November, 2002 (Box-folder 8-5)
  - January-March, 2003 (Box-folder 8-6)
  - April, 2003 (Box-folder 8-7)
  - May, 2003 (Box-folder 8-8)
  - June, 2003 (Box-folder 8-9)
  - July, 2003 (Box-folder 8-10)
  - August, 2003 (Box-folder 8-11)
  - September, 2003 (Box-folder 8-12)
  - October, 2003 (Box-folder 8-13)
  - November, 2003 (Box-folder 8-14)
  - December, 2003 (Box-folder 8-15)
  - Daily schedule, 2001 (Box-folder 9-1)
  - Daily schedule, 2002 (Box-folder 9-2)
  - Daily schedule, 2003 (Box-folder 9-3)
  - Daily schedule, 2004 (Box-folder 9-4)
  - Daily schedule, 2005 (Box-folder 9-5)
  - Daily schedule, 2006 (Box-folder 9-6)
  - Daily schedule, 2007 (Box-folder 9-7)
  - Daily schedule, 2008 (Box-folder 9-8)
- Professional activities, V
  - AASCU, 2007 (Box-folder 10-1)
  - ACE Commission on Women in Higher Education, 2006-2008 (Box-folder 10-2)
  - Correspondence, 2001-2008 (Box-folder 10-3)
  - Correspondence, 2004-2009 (Box-folder 10-4)
  - Council of Presidents, 2006 (Box-folder 10-5)
  - Curriculum vita, circa 2008 (Box-folder 10-6)
  - Economic Development Board, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 10-7)
  - Events, 2001-2008 (Box-folder 10-8)
  - Honors/recognition, 2006 (Box-folder 10-9)
  - Honors/recognition, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 11-1)
  - J-Mac Sightings, 2009 (Box-folder 11-2)
  - National Committee to Unite a Divided America, 2006 (Box-folder 11-3)
  - Leadership, 2001-2008 (Box-folder 11-4)
  - Leadership Ellensburg, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 11-5)
  - News releases, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 11-6)
  - Student events, circa 2000s (Box-folder 11-7)
  - University Bulletin—Messages for President, 2001-2008 (Box-folder 11-8)
- Speeches, VI
  - Campus events, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 11-9)
  - Fall Faculty Conference, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 11-10)
  - Fall Faculty Planning Forum, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 11-11)
  - State and regional, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 11-12)
  - Campus and community events, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 11-13)
  - Recurring ceremonies and events, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 11-14)
  - State, regional, and national venues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 11-15)
  - State of the University Address, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 11-16)
  - Major campus and community events, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 11-17)
  - Recurring campus and community events, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 11-18)
  - State and national venues, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 11-19)
  - State of the University Address, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 11-20)
  - Guest lectures, 2003 (Box-folder 11-21)
  - Fall Faculty Day, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 11-22)
  - Major campus and community events, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 11-23)
  - Recurring campus events, reports, and introductions, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 11-24)
  - State and national venues, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 11-25)
  - State of the University Address, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 11-26)
  - Fall Faculty Day and Staff Forum, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 11-27)
  - Major campus and community events, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 11-28)
  - Recurring campus events, reports, and introductions, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 12-1)
  - State and national venues, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 12-2)
  - State of the University Address, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 12-3)
  - Miscellaneous speeches, 2005 (Box-folder 12-4)
  - Fall Faculty Day and Staff Forum, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 12-5)
  - Major campus and community events, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 12-6)
  - Recurring events, reports, and introductions, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 12-7)
  - State and national venues, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 12-8)
  - State of the University Address, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 12-9)
  - Miscellaneous speeches, January 2006-June 2006 (Box-folder 12-10)
  - Miscellaneous speeches, July 2006-December 2006 (Box-folder 12-11)
  - Articles, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 12-12)
  - Major campus and community events, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 12-13)
  - State of the University Address, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 12-14)
  - Fall Faculty Day and Staff Forum, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 12-15)
  - Major campus and community events, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 12-16)
  - Recurring events, reports, and introductions, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 13-1)
  - State and national venues, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 13-2)
  - State of the University Address, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 13-3)
  - Miscellaneous speeches, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 13-4)
  - Major campus and community events, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 13-5)
  - Recurring events, reports, and introductions, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 13-6)
  - State and national venues, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 13-7)
  - Miscellaneous speeches (Box-folder 13-8)
- Board of Trustees Minutes, VII
  - August 7-8, 2003 (Box-folder 14-1)
  - October 9-10, 2003 (Box-folder 14-2)
  - October 9-10, 2003 (Box-folder 14-3)
  - December 5, 2003 (Box-folder 14-4)
  - December 5, 2003 (Box-folder 14-5)
  - February 13, 2004 (Box-folder 14-6)
  - February 13, 2004 (Box-folder 14-7)
  - March 12, 2004 (Box-folder 14-8)
  - May 7, 2004 (Box-folder 15-1)
  - May 7, 2004 (Box-folder 15-2)
  - May 7, 2004 (Box-folder 15-3)
  - May 26, 2004 (Box-folder 15-4)
  - June 11, 2004 (Box-folder 15-5)
  - June 11, 2004 (Box-folder 15-6)
  - August 5-6, 2004 (Box-folder 15-7)
  - September 30, 2004 (Box-folder 16-1)
  - October 8, 2004 (Box-folder 16-2)
  - October 8, 2004 (Box-folder 16-3)
  - Joint meeting with Edmonds CC Board, November 6, 2004 (Box-folder 16-4)
  - December 3, 2004 (Box-folder 16-5)
  - February 4, 2005 (Box-folder 16-6)
  - February 4, 2005 (Box-folder 16-7)
  - March 4, 2005 (Box-folder 16-8)
  - May 6, 2005 (Box-folder 17-1)
  - June 10, 2005 (Box-folder 17-2)
  - July 25-26, 2005 (Box-folder 17-3)
  - July 25-26, 2005 (Box-folder 17-4)
  - August 2-3, 2005 (Box-folder 17-5)
  - October 6-7, 2005 (Box-folder 17-6)
  - October 6-7, 2005 (Box-folder 17-7)
  - December 2, 2005 (Box-folder 18-1)
  - January 17, 2006 (Box-folder 18-2)
  - January 27, 2006 (Box-folder 18-3)
  - February 3, 2006 (Box-folder 18-4)
  - March 1-2, 2006 (Box-folder 18-5)
  - March 2-3, 2006 (Box-folder 18-6)
  - March 2-3, 2006 (Box-folder 18-7)
  - May 5, 2006 (Box-folder 18-8)
  - May 5, 2006 (Box-folder 18-9)
  - May 23, 2006 (Box-folder 18-10)
  - June 9, 2006 (Box-folder 19-1)
  - June 9, 2006 (Box-folder 19-2)
  - August 3-4, 2006 (Box-folder 19-3)
  - September 26, 2006 (Box-folder 19-4)
  - October 5-6, 2006 (Box-folder 19-5)
  - October 5-6, 2006 (Box-folder 19-6)
  - October 5-6, 2006 (Box-folder 19-7)
  - December 7-8, 2006 (Box-folder 19-8)
  - February 1-2, 2007 (Box-folder 19-9)
  - March 1-2, 2007 (Box-folder 20-1)
  - May 3-4, 2007 (Box-folder 20-2)
  - May 3-4, 2007 (Box-folder 20-3)
  - June 7-8, 2007 (Box-folder 20-4)
  - June 7-8, 2007 (Box-folder 20-5)
- Meeting Notes, VIII
  - Academic affairs issues, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 21-1)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 21-2)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 21-3)
  - Budget issues, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 21-4)
  - Business affairs issues, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 21-5)
  - Faculty Senate issues, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 21-6)
  - Student affairs issues, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 21-7)
  - Student affairs issues, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 21-8)
  - Student affairs issues, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 21-9)
  - University relations issues, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 21-10)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 21-11)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 21-12)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 21-13)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22-1)
  - Alumni issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22-2)
  - Athletics issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22-3)
  - Athletics issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22-4)
  - Athletics issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22-5)
  - Athletics issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22-6)
  - ASCWU Board of Directors issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22-7)
  - Budget Office issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22-8)
  - Business affairs issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22-9)
  - Business affairs issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22-10)
  - Cabinet issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23-1)
  - Equal opportunity issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23-2)
  - Equal opportunity issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23-3)
  - Executive assistant issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23-4)
  - Faculty Senate issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23-5)
  - Government relations issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23-6)
  - Internal audit issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23-7)
  - Ombuds Office issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23-8)
  - President’s Office issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23-9)
  - Student affairs issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23-10)
  - Student affairs issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23-11)
  - Student affairs issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23-12)
  - Student affairs issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23-13)
  - University relations issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23-14)
  - University relations issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23-15)
  - University relations issues, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 24-1)
  - ASCWU-BOD issues, 2003 (Box-folder 24-2)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2003 (Box-folder 24-3)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2003 (Box-folder 24-4)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2003 (Box-folder 24-5)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2003 (Box-folder 24-6)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2003 (Box-folder 24-7)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2003 (Box-folder 24-8)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2003 (Box-folder 25-1)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2003 (Box-folder 25-2)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2003 (Box-folder 25-3)
  - Alumni issues, 2003 (Box-folder 25-4)
  - Athletics issues, 2003 (Box-folder 25-5)
  - Athletics issues, 2003 (Box-folder 25-6)
  - Athletics issues, 2003 (Box-folder 25-7)
  - Budget Office issues, 2003 (Box-folder 25-8)
  - Budget Office issues, 2003 (Box-folder 25-9)
  - Business affairs issues, 2003 (Box-folder 25-10)
  - Business affairs issues, 2003 (Box-folder 26-1)
  - Business affairs issues, 2003 (Box-folder 26-2)
  - Cabinet issues, 2003 (Box-folder 26-3)
  - Cabinet issues, 2003 (Box-folder 26-4)
  - Diversity Council issues, 2003 (Box-folder 26-5)
  - Diversity Council issues, 2003 (Box-folder 26-6)
  - Equal opportunity issues, 2003 (Box-folder 26-7)
  - Equal opportunity issues, 2003 (Box-folder 26-8)
  - Executive Assistant issues, 2003 (Box-folder 26-9)
  - Executive Assistant issues, 2003 (Box-folder 26-10)
  - Faculty Senate issues, 2003 (Box-folder 27-1)
  - Faculty Senate issues, 2003 (Box-folder 27-2)
  - Government relations issues, 2003 (Box-folder 27-3)
  - Government relations issues, 2003 (Box-folder 27-4)
  - High Demand FTE, 2003 (Box-folder 27-5)
  - Internal audit issues, 2003 (Box-folder 27-6)
  - Ombuds Office issues, 2003 (Box-folder 27-7)
  - President’s Office issues, 2003 (Box-folder 27-8)
  - Student affairs issues, 2003 (Box-folder 27-9)
  - Student affairs issues, 2003 (Box-folder 27-10)
  - Student affairs issues, 2003 (Box-folder 27-11)
  - Student affairs issues, 2003 (Box-folder 28-1)
  - Student affairs issues, 2003 (Box-folder 28-2)
  - University relations issues, 2003 (Box-folder 28-3)
  - University relations issues, 2003 (Box-folder 28-4)
  - University relations issues, 2003 (Box-folder 28-5)
  - University relations issues, 2003 (Box-folder 28-6)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2004 (Box-folder 28-7)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2004 (Box-folder 28-8)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2004 (Box-folder 28-9)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2004 (Box-folder 28-10)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2004 (Box-folder 29-1)
  - ASCWU-BOD issues, 2004 (Box-folder 29-2)
  - Athletics issues, 2004 (Box-folder 29-3)
  - Athletics issues, 2004 (Box-folder 29-4)
  - Budget Office issues, 2004 (Box-folder 29-5)
  - Business affairs issues, 2004 (Box-folder 29-6)
  - Business affairs issues, 2004 (Box-folder 29-7)
  - Cabinet issues, 2004 (Box-folder 29-8)
  - Cabinet issues, 2004 (Box-folder 30-1)
  - Cabinet issues, 2004 (Box-folder 30-2)
  - Diversity Council issues, 2004 (Box-folder 30-3)
  - Equal opportunity issues, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 30-4)
  - Executive Assistant issues, 2004 (Box-folder 30-5)
  - Executive Assistant issues, 2004 (Box-folder 30-6)
  - Faculty Senate issues, 2004 (Box-folder 30-7)
  - Government relations issues, 2004 (Box-folder 30-8)
  - Government relations issues, 2004 (Box-folder 30-9)
  - Government relations issues, 2004 (Box-folder 30-10)
  - Government relations issues, 2004 (Box-folder 31-1)
  - Internal audit issues, 2004 (Box-folder 31-2)
  - Ombuds Office issues, 2004 (Box-folder 31-3)
  - President’s Office issues, 2004 (Box-folder 31-4)
  - President’s Office issues, 2004 (Box-folder 31-5)
  - Student affairs issues, 2004 (Box-folder 31-6)
  - Student affairs issues, 2004 (Box-folder 31-7)
  - Student affairs issues, 2004 (Box-folder 31-8)
  - Student trustee issues, 2004 (Box-folder 31-9)